There was a huge demand from the candidates, Sir, please
bring part time jobs.  So
in this video I have brought for you
a part time
work from home job from a big organization like ICICI Lombard.
Anyone who has passed 12th or has a diploma or graduate can apply.
Ok?  The best part is there is
no need to invest any money.
You can earn a good amount.
You can work here when you have time.
Because here you have to
work directly with ICICI LBT.
You can work when you have time.   There
is reliable support.  Instant policy
is insurance.  There is no need to do any paper work.
And payouts are available here timely.
Products are given here.
How much commission will be received is also given here.  The
link to apply is
in the description box.  You can go and register.   Please
like the video and you
can also support me by subscribing to my channel.
Allah Hafiz.